<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <packageId>wishRobber.isekaiguildpatches</packageId>
    <name>Isekai Guild Patches</name>
    <author>wishRobber</author>
    <description>Quality-of-life patches for Isekai RPG Leveling's Adventurer's Guild, bundled into one add-on.

What it does:
- Every guild listing becomes a local Bounty. The target spawns on your map, hostile and attacking, from a random map edge, instead of at a remote world site or as a creature that just wanders off. Some marks arrive alone, some with a rank-scaled pack.
- Bounties scale to your party's rank. They roll against your colonists' actual ranks (F to SSS) instead of a flat level cap, so a strong party gets tougher targets and a weak one is never overwhelmed.
- Listings are mirrored into RimWorld's normal Quests tab, so you accept them from home without traveling to the world board, and the vanilla quest-expiry alert is hidden.
- Cleaner rewards: strips the random weapons, armor, components and drugs, and adds more mana essence, reinforcement cores, rebirth orbs, star fragments and healing potions at higher ranks.

Requires Isekai RPG Leveling and its Guild Faction Add-on (plus Harmony). A lightweight Harmony patch, no new items or defs, safe to add to or remove from a save at any time.</description>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.6</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    <modDependencies>
        <li>
            <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
            <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
        <li>
            <packageId>JellyCreative.IsekaiLeveling</packageId>
            <displayName>ISEKAI RPG LEVELING</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/3657580708</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
        <li>
            <packageId>Poupun.GuildFactionAddon</packageId>
            <displayName>GUILD FACTION ADD-ON - Isekai RPG Leveling</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/3718568958</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
    </modDependencies>
    <loadAfter>
        <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
        <li>JellyCreative.IsekaiLeveling</li>
        <li>Poupun.GuildFactionAddon</li>
    </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
